Tell me about the thrill of being
selected by the Dolphins. Did it
surprise you and and tell me about the
the phone call and your meetings with
them prior to the draft?
Yeah, man. Definitely surprised me, man.
I you know, just sitting there watching
the draft obviously seeing different
things go down. And you know, I finally
saw my phone go off. And I answered and
you know, my my service was a little
spotty so I couldn't really hear too
well. I had to start moving around the
house, but once I was able to talk talk
with everybody, man, it was just a great
feeling, man. Just understanding, you
know, a team a team values me enough to
to be able to trade up and grab me, man.
And
like you said, pre-draft meetings went
went great with them and I definitely
connected with with them and their
staff. And man, I'm just excited to get
out there and play some ball, man.
Isaiah?
What's going on, Chris? Isaiah Smalls
from the Miami Herald. Welcome to Miami.
How you feeling?
I'm I'm feeling great, man. Super
excited to be out there, man.
That's what's up. That's what's up. Uh
Sullvan spoke highly of your character
and your approach to the game, even
going as far as saying that you play
with an edge. If you can kind of
describe what that edge means to to you
and why is it that you play with that?
Yeah, for sure, man. I feel like my edge
is I could just describe it as being
being non-stop relentless, man. And I
feel like that that just goes
with the culture that I built here being
at San Diego State the last 4 years.
That's what we preached, man.
That we weren't always the most talented
defense on the field, but regardless,
you know, effort going out outlasts
skill every time. So, just going out
there with the approach that I'm going
to give 100% on the field whether, you
know, whether I got the car or don't.
Like regardless of what I'm doing, I'm
going to be at 100% always.
That's what's up. That's what's up. And
second one for you. I'm sure you know
Half was a secondary coach. Like that's
how he got his start on defense. You
being his first pick in the secondary
certainly means something. From the
conversation that you remember,
what did he say he liked about your
game?
Um
Uh probably just said that that he feel
like I'm a polished player, man. Like I
I excel in different areas and I feel
like
you know, just taking this next jump and
being able to work with him and work
under him is just going to help me be be
the best player I could be and just keep
keep on improving.
Well, appreciate you, man. Yes, sir.
Marcel?
How's it going, Chris? Marcel
Louis-Jacques with ESPN.
Congratulations, man. Welcome to Miami.
I guess trading one paradise for the
other, right? Going San Diego.
That's crazy.
But uh you said something that was I
think was really interesting just now.
For your 4 years at San Diego State and
that is a rarity in college football.
Now, what was it about your situation
that made you say, "I'm staying where
I'm put. I'm staying where I signed for
all 4 years. I'm not transferring."
Yeah, I feel like
you know, after I got my start my my
junior year and I played that season,
you know, a couple teams started calling
for me to to you know, obviously hit the
portal and go there, but I feel like at
the end of the day, my dream was to get
to where I am right now, man. I felt
like I didn't want to go somewhere and
put uncertainties in the air whereas,
you know, I get a bag of money, but it's
also like who am I going to be competing
against? Who am I going to be playing
with? You know, what scheme are they
going to be running? And I'm like, you
know what? I know what I'm going to do
here at State. And you know, my dad
always always preached to me, man, that
you know, if you're talented enough,
they're going to come find you, man. So,
you know, I put I put my head down and
just worked, man, and stayed there. And
I feel like, you know, I I have no
regrets, man. Exactly what me and my dad
preached, man. I feel like it came to
life for sure.
Appreciate that, man. Nice to meet you
and congrats once again.
>> Yes, sir. I appreciate it.
David?
Chris, congratulations and welcome to to
Miami. Welcome to the to the Dolphins,
man.
Yes, sir.
The So, the combine you had was was
sensational. How do you think the
athleticism you showed at that event
that translates onto the field? How do
you use that athleticism on on the
football field?
Yeah, for sure, man. Just being able to
go out there and show it not only on
tape, but also, you know, get the
concrete numbers down. I feel like
definitely helped me. As far as using
that on the field, it just helps me you
know, play the game I like to play like
like being ultra physical and ultra
patient, man. Obviously having some
speed, I could be more patient I'm
rushing. I don't have to panic as much
as, you know, some other guys may. But
God blessed me with this talent I have
and you know, I just turn around and
thank him by using it on the field.
And if I could follow up,
I know what when we spoke to Jeff Hafley
and he mentioned how he evaluates
corners. He he he views it as three
levels. His first, can they win at the
line of scrimmage? Then can they win on
in the intermediate routes? And then can
they win down the field? How do you view
yourself as far as covering those three
aspects?
Yeah, really all three, man. I feel like
obviously I can improve all three as
well, but I feel like I'm sound in all
three and
obviously just understanding, you know,
if you lose phase one and two, you know,
phase three is where the money happens,
man. Where the ball comes. So, being
able to to you know, recover and be able
to make a play, you know, whenever or
wherever you at in relation to the
receiver, man. I feel like that's the
most important one, but uh definitely
just excited to to keep working on my
craft and keep improving.